<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Introduction</title>
    <link>http://sunfactory.pt/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Introduction</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="http://sunfactory.pt/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Sun Glasses</title>
      <link>http://sunfactory.pt/projects/sunglasses/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sunfactory.pt/projects/sunglasses/</guid>
      <description>We create from scatch The objective of this project was to demonstrate that it is possible to create a sustainable product factory with plastic waste, human energy and solar thermal energy.
With the help of Recua we reproduced the solar injection process, invented by volks.eco and Plastok.
After building our machines,we co-developed and manufactored this sunglasses from scratch.
We are able to take care of every step between the idea and the final product in your hand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Work Shop</title>
      <link>http://sunfactory.pt/projects/workshop/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sunfactory.pt/projects/workshop/</guid>
      <description>We can prove it and teach it After more than a year of experience in plastic recycling with solar thermal energy, we are available to teach you and demonstrate the effectiveness of our process.
Want to learn how solar plastic injection works. take a look at our Workshop Agenda.
We can show you how to create recycled plastic products with solar thermal energy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Machines</title>
      <link>http://sunfactory.pt/projects/machines/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sunfactory.pt/projects/machines/</guid>
      <description>We create our machines Our manual solar-concentrating machines are the key to the ecological production of recycled plastic objects.
Based on the shared know-how, we have built, tested, used and characterized the plastic injection process using solar energy.
After more than a year of using the solar thermal process, we were able to list the optimization points for a process guaranteeing the production of machines and products on a larger scale.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
